Guide to the Laura Gray Political Cartoons GRAPHICS.013
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Cartoons
  - Stalinism, Apr 1950, Apr 1956, undated (Box 5, Folder 14, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Stalinism: Political Prisoner, Jan 15, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Stevenson, Adlai: Campaign, Sep 1, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Stone, Lucy, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Syria, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Taft, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Taxes, Oct 1945-Aug 1954 (Box 1, Folder 20-21, Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Tidelands Oil Steal, May-Sep 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21, Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Till, Emmett, Sep-Oct 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6, Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Truman, President Harry, Jan 1947-Dec 1948, undated (Box 6, Folder 6-8, Flat-file-folder 1, Box 3, Folder 14, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Truman, President Harry: Campaign, Jun 2, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Truman, President Harry: Christmas, Dec 1949, Dec 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22, Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Truman, President Harry: Colonial Revolts, Jan-Mar 1952 (Box 3, Folder 14, Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Truman, President Harry: Excess Profits Tax, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Truman, President Harry: Housing, May 2, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Truman, President Harry: MacArthur, Dec 11, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Truman, President Harry: Opa Bill, Jul-Aug 1946 (Box 3, Folder 14, Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Truman, President Harry: Truman Doctrine, Apr 5, 1947 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Truman, President Harry: Witch-Hunts, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified, Jun 1946, undated (Box 3, Folder 14, Box 6, Folder 9)
  - USSR: Peace Conference, Aug 24, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wall Street, Jul 1945-Sep 1948 (Flat-file-folder 1, Box 6, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Wall Street: Christmas, Dec 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wall Street: Elections, Nov 3, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Wall Street: Imperialism, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Wall Street: Labor, Feb 15, 1947 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Wall Street: War, Oct 4, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - War: A-Bomb, Oct 3, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - War: Fair Deal/War Pact, Jan 1949-Jan 1950 (Box 6, Folder 2, Box 3, Folder 15)
  - War: Imperialism, Jul 18, 1949 (Flat-file-folder 5, Box 3, Folder 15)
  - War Budget, Feb 1952, undated (Box 1, Folder 23, Folder 11)
  - War Budget: Eisenhower, Jan 28, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - War Contracts, Oct 25, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - War Contracts: GM, Feb 2, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - War Labor Board, Jul 1944-Feb 1945, undated (Box 1, Folder 23, Box 6, Folder 2, Folder 12)
  - War Labor Board: Little Steel Formula, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - War Preparations: Housing, May 4, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - War Profits, Aug 1945, Apr 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - War Profits: Cover of the Militant, Leon Trotsky Memorial Issue, Aug 18, 1945 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - War Profits: Labor, Aug 1955, Dec 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - World War II, Oct 1945, Mar 1946, undated (Box 6, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Folder 8)
  - World War II: Army Jim Crow, Oct 28, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - World War II: Atlantic Charter, Dec 30, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - World War II: No Strike Pledge, Jun 10, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - World War II: Socialism, May 11, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - World War II: Wall Street, Apr-Oct 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Yugoslavia, Jun 5, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Yugoslavia: Capitalism, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Yugoslavia: Tito, Marshall, May 29, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series II: Reference Binders
  Contains 9 reference binders, which consist of photocopies of 512 of the original cartoons. The cartoons in this series are individually numbered. There are 2 binders which depict Gray's "Rich Bitch" series. Also contains clippings of Gray's cartoons as they appeared in The Militant from 1951-1953.
  - Binders 1-5, 1944-1952 (Box 7)
  - Binders 6-9, 1945-1947, 1953-1957, undated (Box 8)
  - Cartoon Clippings, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)